Welcome back guys, welcome back to a new vlog, welcome back to a new week.
I hope you guys are all doing amazing.
It is Wednesday, I just finished a modeling job, it's lunchtime, I'm gonna eat.
But before I do that, I have got a package.
We have some really interesting silverware that I bought secondhand.
You guys know I love this website called Silency, this is where I buy most of little pieces here and there secondhand.
I've never bought actual furniture but I'd love to.
In the kitchen, one thing that I purchased there secondhand was this mug and little plate set.
And I got six pieces and I got this for, if I remember, like 30 or 35 euros, the six pieces.
So it's really, really great deal.
And I love this.
I think it looks really good with my kitchen in general and with the vibe of the house.
It's from the brand Christophe, which is a very famous luxury French silverware tableware decoration
brand.
It was established I think in like 1830-1850 so it's really really old.
It's very well known and so they have many many things there from them so if you're looking for some Christophe pieces you can definitely head on
that website called Célenci.
Oh my god and I got these spoons.
I fell in love with spoons and I got them.
I don't know if I'll be using them daily but I just thought it was such a gorgeous piece to have on a table when you invite people
at dessert or things like that.
I thought it looked really good.
So here is the box as you can see the brand Christophe.
Are we ready?
And here they are look how cute I love this little black detail I love that they're gold I
think they're gonna look so gorgeous look at that so gorgeous I love it I really fell in love with this little detail I think it just made
it so modern and cool and I think it's just really gonna bring something to a table love it also since we're looking at vintage kind of decor
my mom gave me one of her presents that she got at her wedding at the time in Japan which is a Givenchy
plate so chic so
freaking chic and I love it because it's like a wedding gift from her wedding with my dad and I I think it's such a precious little
thing to have in my kitchen and when you invite people.
So I guess we're going to be spending a lot of time in this kitchen.
Okay, so it's nighttime.
It's dinner time.
And my mom was supposed to come to eat at my place for dinner.
So I was going to make a meal with her help, but her train is late.
So she's not going to make it on time.
So she's not going to make it actually for dinner anyway.
I'm still gonna make the meal and try to make it as good as her.
It's what she called I think in
Japanese
Shogoyaki It's like a very thinly sliced pork in ginger and a little bit of soy sauce and all that and it was
Fabulous when she made it last time she was here and I've been craving it ever since so we're having that tonight It's going to be rice the
little shredded pork.
I got this.
I love this.
This is marinated radish.
It's so good.
I buy all these things at a place called Kmart in Paris.
They have several ones.
I love it.
A little athiru, edamame.
Always buy these at Kmart too.
She said put everything in a bowl, just mix it with salt, pepper, grated ginger, olive oil, and let it sit a little bit.
So we're gonna do that.
So you add all the ginger, grated ginger, pepper, salt, olive oil.
And then put it in the fridge.
I'm going to show you how I make my rice.
My mom taught me how to make rice when I was a kid.
In Brazil we eat a lot of rice, we eat rice and beans so it's just something that we eat so often and really really young my mom
taught me how to make rice and this is how I make it and honestly I feel like it's the best way.
It just tastes so delicious.
Before I show how I make my rice, I just poured myself a glass of water and it remembered, it reminded me of a video I saw today
that is really interesting.
It's about stress.
So there's this teacher that pours a glass of water and he asks his students, what is the weight of the glass of Water?
And then the students kind of give more like concrete answers.
And what he says, it says the absolute weight of a glass of water does matter.
It depends on how long you hold on to it.
So it means that if you hold on to it for a minute, it's not going to do anything.
If you hold on to it for an hour, you're going to start to get a little, you know, your arm's going to start to hurt.
If you hold on to it all day, you're going to get really numb and tired of holding the glass of water.
And so he says, this is the same thing about the little worries and stress in life.
If you think about them just for a little bit, it's okay.
If you think about them for a little longer, it can start to hurt.
If you keep thinking about your stress, the things that stresses you out about life for too long, then it's going to paralyze you and
prevent you from doing anything great.
So now I kind of have this like little thing in my mind, this little note where I'm like, okay, when you have a worry, let go.
So this is how I make my rice.
I put the heat on very medium to low, some olive oil here.
I add this cup of rice, and I stir the olive oil
and the rice until it becomes kind of transparent.
And then whatever cup you use, whatever amount of rice you put, you put the same amount of water but two
times.
And then I cover it up and leave it on for like good 15 minutes.
I cooked.
And you know what?
I didn't work out this morning.
And I'm like, I'm home.
I'm alone.
My peace.
Should I go work out?
Like a little, you know, like a little, a little workout, a little something.
Should I?
You know what I want right now?
I wish this phase right now that I'm in, the motivation
phase, the showing up for myself phase was done because it's the hardest one.
Because I know that once I start a class and I'm in it, I'm not even questioning it anymore.
Just have to get to it.
Let me just put a legging on and I'm going to do it.
And I made it.
Motivated myself.
I'm going to do a little 15-minute arm workout and 15-minute ab workout.
And I love Pilates by Izzy because they're short, but they're super spicy.
In three.
In two.
On this next one, open the arms and hold strong through your core, lift your hips up, bring
the weights to tap together overhead, open out to the side, lower down, and then close, open, lift,
relax your shoulders, tap, lower, hinge, gonna add that dip of the hips back in, ready, all the way up,
as you come down, you dip, squeeze the glutes and the core, lift, dip,
and lift.
And I have an event tomorrow night, and I know I'm going to do a little fake tanning tonight, like a little, you know, usual glow that I
use, which is use this on the body, which is the lotion, it's very subtle, but it just gives a really nice glow.
And on the face, I use this, the face by Tan Luxe.
Both are from Tan Luxe.
Um, you just add a few drops into your moisturizer.
Don't do like my boyfriend that used this literally as if it was a serum, and he just like goes like that on his face, crazy.
But he is also addicted to this product ever since he's tried it from me.
He's like, it just makes me look so much more alive.
And it does.
Well, I'm first gonna exfoliate my body.
I'm to use this from Natura.
My mom bought me this.
It's the body scrub in the Castagna line.
It smells divine, and it leaves a very nice feeling to the skin.
I'm going to use this body wash by Nécessaire in the Eucalyptus.
I love this.
I took my nail polish off.
Off.
My nails have been not great lately, and so I was at Monoprix, which sometimes I buy some things there, um, and you know, I
tried before the one from ICI, I think it ICI, which is the Hard to Resist Advanced, works really well.
You supposed to put two coats and then whatever nail polish you want.
This works well.
But I don't know.
I went by this brand.
It's called Mavala.
It's a pretty known brand, and they had these like nail shields, and it was in two phases.
So I was like, oh, maybe this is really good.
So it comes in a pack together, and you have phase one and phase two, which is nice because it has a little.
Bit of a natural nude color, so it's perfect.
That's all I have to say.
Didn't do anything for me.
Um, my nails kept breaking.
I've been using this for like 10 days, I would say.
No difference.
Anyway, time to get this dinner finished.
The rice is cooked.
I'm going to show it to you.
Final result on the rice.
This is what it should look like.
It doesn't burn.
It's really good.
Edamame is ready, just to snack on.
And then I'm going to make a little red cabbage and carrot salad.
And I made a sauce that I really love.
It's olive oil, apple cider vinegar, rice vinegar, and a little bit of soy sauce, and it's really delicious.
You can also add, which makes it super yummy, sesame oil.
Really, really good.
Here is the final
result.
Super simple but super yummy.
I tried this, and it's turned out pretty good.
Good morning, guys.
Today is shipment day.
We've received all of our production yesterday afternoon, and it is time we pack all the orders.
I am so excited to get everything out.
We do have one situation that I hope is going to get solved today, but we, a box is missing from the production.
A full box is missing with one specific style and one specific size, and that is a huge problem.
So I hope, I hope, I hope we are gonna get this solved, because it would really be complicated.
Great news, guys, the box has been found, because I told them we had a box missing.
Oh yeah, and it's been found, and we have it this morning.
That is, I woke up today, I was kind of stressed.
Really?
Yeah, no, I was not.
It was said partially delivered.
Partially delivered, you know those things.
We have an event with Lisa tonight, and we just received the invitation, and look how pretty this is.
The detail and the paper, so gorgeous.
Our little packing station is ready, just like last time.
My mom did, uh, catering, and she brought this.
This is one of our favorite Brazilian candies, Seven Bello.
We've put my mom to contribution.
She identifies the style, and she preps them in the silk tops.
There, look at
her,
um, unpacking.
And of course, had to put some music in the background, and I recently rediscovered a song I love, and I had to share it with you guys.
It's from the band called Hers, and it's called "What Once Was," and the melody of this music is so,
I don't know, fresh but also nostalgic, and I just could listen to the song over and over again.
So we only have 10 orders to go.
And here is our first batch of the day.
We need to bring everything at the post office now.
Good evening, I am getting ready for the event I told you guys about earlier.
I'm debating with myself.
I think I'm gonna wear a full-on black look from Becking Bridge.
But then I think, what do I do with the makeup?
I kind of wanted to do something different.
I did my face like skin base, so nothing new here.
And I was like, should I do a smoky eye?
But not the brown one that I usually do, like a black one.
But then we know the problem about that is one, I don't have that much time to mess up, and if I mess up,
it's gonna look bad, bad.
So should I, should I not?
I'm like, should I?
It would be kind of this, this.
Am I crazy?
Let me see.
It's not that pigmented.
It kind of would look...
It could look really cool and very different.
I don't know if I want to take the risk.
I went for it, but I did it in a very subtle way.
I really need to do a makeup session where I really do a really black, smoky eye, just to see the lines.
So it goes more into the brown, but that's okay.
Get whatever excess is here.
I'm gonna go here, under.
Trust the process.
This point, don't have a choice to do that.
Oh my god, guys, I dislike my makeup so much right now, and I, oh no, but you know, you can't win every
time.
So this is, oh my god, nothing's right in the light.
I don't know.
I don't like it.
What do you guys think?
I'm just gonna hide it with my hair like that.
We are wearing a simple black pants, little backless top by Beckenbridge.
So let's do it.
It's like this, and it has this like really pretty detail.
Look at that.
You can do it however you want.
It's little buttons that goes all around the pants and.
You have the same detail on the top and the back.
So pretty and chic.
See?
That little button detail keeps on going here.
I'm just going to go like that, and I'm not even going to wear a jacket because it's 23 degrees, and it's kind of the beginning of summer.
Okay, you know what's going on?
I know what's going on.
This is a type of look that would have looked really good if I had fake tanned, but I didn't.
Because I fell asleep last night, and I forgot.
It is what it is.
Okay, that's kind of cute.
Just do that.
It's cute.
I'm going to wear heels, a little bag.
Let's get out.
Picked up the sister.
So,
so.
All right, guys, I just got back from London.
Today is Sunday.
The London part will be a vlog on its own that will be out in a week, just so you know.
And I am getting organized for a trip.
I don't know if I've said it yet in the vlog, but Lisa and I and our two boyfriends are all leaving for Bali on
Tuesday, which we're all so, so excited about.
It's a little getaway that we're doing for two weeks, the four of us, and it's going to be so much fun.
As I'm packing, I'm kind of looking at what I want to bring.
And as I told you guys in my last vlog, I have received a lot of makeup gifting.
The three brands that I got lately is Merit, NARS, and Dior Beauty.
And I just wanted to dig into it, and honestly, I am so attached to the makeup products that I use every day that I have a hard
time being like, "Oh, let me switch this up for today."
We're gonna start with base.
So base, I got different types of products.
I'm gonna start with the Forever Skin Glow by Dior.
It's the shade 1N.
Okay, so I always apply in the back of my hand.
I'm going to start with one pump.
It's very, very um fluid.
You guys know I love the Dior Backstage foundation.
In terms of consistency, this one's a little bit more liquid, as you can see.
See, it's already running on my hand.
I'm going to use my Hourglass foundation brush.
I love to just pack some product onto the brush like that, so it gives a very natural finishing onto
the skin.
This is like nothing on your skin.
So that is already a huge positive point for me, because I don't like
makeup that feels too heavy on the skin, that looks too heavy.
I am pretty particular with that.
Look at the difference.
Here I have nothing on, and here I have the foundation.
Such a big difference.
See, it color corrected all my redness, everything.
Wow, I had to get up to go see it in the mirror of my bathroom, which is where I usually do my makeup, just to see how
it looks.
And it looks so good.
I'm obsessed, guys.
Next, I got the Complexion Stick by Merit.
It's called the Minimalist.
So basically, this stick, you can use it all over your face.
And I thought I'd just color correct under my eye, around my nose, just to test the consistency
and the coverage for you guys.
Merit is truly a brand that, to me, has nailed the no-makeup makeup look.
If you're someone that doesn't want products that feel too heavy, that want things that just look super um natural,
Merit is for you.
You're gonna really, really love this brand for that.
Oh, that's very pretty too.
I think it did do a little correction.
Same here.
Very light consistency, and it blended really easily.
That's so pretty.
Hmm.
We need to do, of course, bronzer.
We're going to use the Merit Bronze Balm Sheer.
Very curious to try this.
I tried it on my hand in the last vlog, and it looked very serum-like.
This is shade Clay.
It's, oh my god, it's so pretty.
Look at that.
It's like so shiny.
It looks like a candy directly on my cheek.
Like, I would then I'm going to use the smaller part of the brush and blend it in.
Wow.
Okay.
It's extremely subtle.
It blends in.
Did you see that?
It blended in a second.
I think I can be a little bit more intense with it if I kind of want more color into my skin.
I brush and go to my forehead like that.
When I do bronzer, I kind of do this like, this is the placement for me.
So I go a little bit over in the forehead.
I always do a little swipe here.
And then, of course, the cheek, and then down a. Little bit here.
Note that if you're someone that loves a pretty present bronzer, you're not going to like this.
You're going to want something that's a little bit more intense.
For example, the Balm by Makeup by Mario or the bronzer, the serum bronzer by Makeup by Mario.
I think you'd prefer it to this.
This is very, very subtle.
I have another bronzer.
I don't want to try it too because I want to put it on my lids also because I don't have any eye product, but I love doing
this to blend everything in.
I have the stick bronzer by Yore in shade Light
Fair, really pretty as well.
And oh, what am I doing?
Okay, I kind of want to...
Okay, I'm gonna just gonna make this look a little bit...
Yeah, just want my cheek to be a little bit more bronzed.
See how this one just made it warmer?
This is beautiful too.
Wow, we're gonna do blush.
And for blush, we're gonna use Your Backstage Rosy Glow in shade number 12 Rosewood.
The packaging of this is...
I have no...
This is so pretty, like that.
Oh my God, it's so pigmented.
Wow, okay, I didn't expect that.
Oh, this is pretty.
As usual, I go upwards, a little bit on the nose.
Ooh la la la la la.
Okay, a little goes a really long way.
Wow, I'm looking crazy.
Am I looking crazy?
Wait, I do love cream products.
Cream bronzer, cream blushes, just feels nicer.
It just feels like it looks better.
It tracks the sunshine, looks beautiful in pictures.
So, oh la la, c'est trop beau.
I do enjoy taking whatever bronzer powder or stick bronzer to do on my eyelids.
I think eyeshadow is an important step because it just brings that little contour to your eyes that
makes them pop.
So I personally can't go without some kind of eyeshadow.
See how it just opened my eye in a way that on the other side is just not as opened.
So there we've done the eyeshadow.
So this is great.
This means you can do your bronzer, you can do your eyes.
So that's great if you like to not have many products in your home or just want to travel light.
You can travel only with this.
That's a great point.
I also have a Hot Escape cheek palette by Nars, and here you have Laguna 01,
Laguna, and shade 01 Ophelia, highlighter powder, Thrill blush, and Bad Behavior blush.
Ooh, Lara.
Look how pretty this is.
This is coming to Bali because I feel like this can be such a pretty kind of highlighter.
This can be such a pretty highlighter.
Love this type of pink.
It's kind of a universal pink.
It's gorgeous on anyone.
And this is the bronzer.
And I think it could look really, really good.
I'm gonna use, I'm gonna use this as a highlighter.
Are we ready?
Use this angled brush.
Is it?
Oh, look.
Oh, whoa.
Look at that.
Oh, it's so pretty.
I love it.
It's kind of that wet look.
Are we ready?
I'm going to go over here.
Oh, my God.
Do you see it?
Ooh.
This is vibes.
This for summer is vibe.
Oh my God, so pretty.
Okay, do you see this?
Oh, it's gorgeous.
Wow, and now we're gonna do mascara, Climax in Explicit Black.
This is what it looks like.
I love this packaging, that's very pretty.
I love this red tip.
When you put mascara on, is put a mirror, put it down, look down, and then do that.
I feel like it's the best way to put your mascara on easily and not put anything onto your makeup.
So since it grips well and then you pull it up, it gives a great lift.
Hmm.
Okay.
So mascara, no mascara.
See the difference?
It's looking good, huh?
Okay, this is what I like about this mascara and I am picky.
It's brought a lot of lift.
It looks really pretty, but see how it didn't do any clumps of anything.
And that is so important.
I do not like mascara that look clumpy or that look there's too much on each lash.
See how my lashes are still very beautifully defined.
There's not too much product on it, but it still gave that wow effect.
Very pretty.
So we're going to use, I got a lip liner from NARS, is the Rosebud.
Oh, this is pretty.
It's a nice shade.
Oh, it's very pink.
It's not what I usually use, but we're trying new things today.
Okay, here it is.
So it's kind of a pinkish, orangish kind of lip.
Then in lip products, I have the Merit Lipstick in shade Baby, which is exactly the type of shade I love.
This is kind of pinkish brownish.
And then let's bring a little bit of gloss.
Then I have the Dior Addict lip oil in shade 77, rosy candy.
Really pretty.
And they're very comfortable on the lips.
Oh, that is so pretty.
So it's just very like transparent, but because it has some shimmer
in, I'll just see gives kind of that golden finish.
So pretty.
And so that's it, guys.
Here is the final makeup.
Let me know what you think.
Let me know what product maybe you already have and love.
But yeah, this looks really, really nice.
I just saw myself also in the mirror once again, where I usually do my makeup and my makeup looks really pretty.
Good morning, guys.
It's the day before the trip.
And I don't think, I don't know about you guys, I don't think I've ever had a day prior to a trip that wasn't hectic and with a
list of 1,000 things to do before we go.
The first thing we're doing this morning is we're going to the tailor.
We going to try to beg him to do an alteration on the dress that I bought.
I bought a dress when I was in London and it needs to be shortened and so I gonna go and beg him to see if he can
do that today and I pick it up
tonight.
Okay, it's done.
He said it's today 6 p.m., so it's perfect.
Second step of the day.
I am to go get my nails done.
I'm going to do a little gel nail manicure.
I thought I'd do it there in Bali and then I thought to myself, I don't want to waste my time doing my nails.
I'd rather be doing something else on vacation.
But I also love when my nails look good the whole time on vacation.
I hate it when they break or they look bad or whatever, so gel nail it is.
It's
time, guys, we're packing for Bali, so I am starting to put things a little bit on the side.
Um, the thing about trips like these, so this time we're saying two, two months, no, not two months, two weeks in Bali.
How I've been packing, how I've been like editing things.
So first of all, Bali to me is like a high summer closet, so these are all the pieces that I have tucked away in my closet because
it's not pieces that I usually wear in Paris, especially certain dresses and skirts and things like that.
So basically, I'm going to pull everything out and then see what I want to bring from that collection.
I would say there's many, many things that I've had for many years but I still wear them.
Only thing I feel I can show you guys is what I purchased recently.
I purchased, this is such a pretty purchase, this is kind of a sarong skirt from Rat and
Boa, and on the sides you basically can tie it up however you want, make it short, make it long.
It has a nice little detail like that.
It's so pretty.
Summer Swim actually gifted me a two-piece that's going to look absolutely perfect with this.
Look at that, so cute together.
They also have Rat and Boa also has the bikini that actually goes with this sarong in the same print, but I like to mix and match and
I feel like these two greens really complement each other well.
Also gifted me a one piece and I love their one pieces because they're so super sexy
and always really well cut.
How does this work?
Okay, so it's like this.
See, it's brown, it has this keyhole, it has this pretty detail, it has this pretty detail.
I love this.
Even I could wear this, you know, with like white linen trousers, go for a little cocktail at sunset.
It's a pretty, um, swimsuit that could be a top and bodysuit top.
I've been gifted this dress from the brand Fenners, which I'm so excited.
I'm being very colorful on this suitcase, but this is gonna look so pretty.
It's like a big prince, a big flower printed, and I think this is very much Bali vibes, high summer vibes.
I'm very happy about this.
This is a Rat and Boa dress that I've had for many years and I love because it's long, it's really fun to wear, it's low
back, and it just always works in this type of environment.
So this I am definitely putting aside.
I'm doing it first, like I put everything I think I love and.
Then I edit it.
Another dress I love to bring is my Araki dress.
It's the one with the bodysuit and this like integrated skirt.
It's always so pretty and so perfect for this type of trip.
Definitely bringing this little Ouijan dress that I purchased last summer.
It's like this and it's like this and then you put it around your neck.
They now actually made it into a dress that's without the neck piece and I kind of love it too.
And I think it's in black and butter yellow or something like that.
Very, very fun dress to have.
Remember I told you guys I forgot my New Year's Eve dress when we went to La Réunion that I bought on Lioness.
And so we have that.
So it's just a simple kind of lace dress.
And it has this kind of open detail in the front.
I bought this very, I just bought this actually.
It's a simple tube dress.
I bought this at Zara.
I will link it down below.
It's perfect.
Just a perfect, simple little summer dress when you just want something that is still super hot,
but very easy to wear.
Crochet short that I bought in Bali.
Actually, I love this pair of shorts.
I always bring it with me.
And I'm going to go back to the store where I bought this.
Well, it's not a store.
It's a stand in a market, specific stand.
And I'm going to go back and see if she has others in other colors, but I'm definitely packing this.
It's the same style, but in a longer midi version is a Rat and Boa.
They still have it too.
This is such a beautiful piece to have for summer.
The brown is perfect.
You have buttons so you can play with the décolleté.
It doesn't have to be this low.
And it just looks great with flats.
It looks great with high heel sandals.
It's a great, great piece to have, honestly.
I really love this.
It's really, really gorgeous.
For sunglasses, I'm packing these four because I feel they're very different.
This one are the Heaven Mayhem ones.
This is a Chanel that I bought many years ago.
This one is from Velia and this one's from Velia.
Like this, I have a smaller size, a full black one, a more, you know, bigger mask vibe and
a more dainty kind of chic one.
So I feel I have everything covered in terms of styles.
I'm also bringing this little camera.
It's so fun to have these type of cameras.
It just makes some really cool pictures so I can't wait to kind of document the whole trip with this little baby.
But to finish I have to say that I am so excited to go back to Bali.
If you're new to this channel and you might not know this, I lived in Bali for two years.
I moved there at the time, I think in 2021 with my ex-companion, if I can call him like that.
And in 2023, I decided to break up and I packed my bags and I came back to Paris.
And honestly, it's been the best decision ever.
My life has changed so much since then.
And in so many ways.
2023 was such a hard but extremely transformative year for myself.
I had to take some really, really hard decisions.
I had to go through some really hard times.
And that year was extremely intense, but it really just, I don't know, transformed me.
And I always have something special for Bali because I love Bali.
I feel like it always feels like my home and it's also a place where I think I grew a lot and I, it
just, I don't know, it gave me a lot of courage.
It gave me everything that I needed to kind of find myself to understand what I want and in many, many ways.
So it's a place that I really hold close to my heart so I'm very, very happy to go back there.
And I recently heard someone say this, I think was on a podcast, that said we are always faced with having
to make decisions in life and instead of thinking, oh, did I make the right one or this or that, you should always just once you've made a
decision, then it, you have to do everything that it takes to make sure that it is the best decision you've ever made.
And I think that's a great philosophy to be like, I feel like a lot of people sometimes are a little scared to take decision.
And then when they do, they're kind of like, see, I shouldn't.
Have done this.
I shouldn't have done that.
And I think that it's important that you take a decision.
And once you're into it, you stick to it, and you make it the best ever.
And I think that was, I really align with this philosophy.
This was the last time I was in Bali.
That was my last day.
Bali, the 16th of May, 2023.
A new chapter starts for me.
And I had taken these flowers from my garden.
And I put them here, and I dried them.
And I don't know, this page is like super special for me in my journal.
And I think I'm going to be closing this chapter.
And I'm gonna get the same flowers, and I'm gonna dry them too.
I feel it's a moment.
So here we are, guys.
This is the end of this little at-home prep vlog.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Next time you see me, we're going to London, and then we'll go to Bali.
All right, guys, I hope you enjoyed this vlog.
I wish you all a beautiful day or a beautiful night, wherever you are, and I'll catch you guys in my next video.
Bye, guys.
Thank you.